Guide to the Free to Dance Records, 1987-2004
American Dance Festival Archives Durham, N.C., USA
- Photographic Materials, 1995-2001 and undated, 2.25 linear feet (Box 18)
  - Production Snapshots: Prints and Negatives, 1998-1999, 1 linear foot, 62 envelopes (Box 19)
    4"x6" color and black and white snapshots of various aspects of the production of Free to Dance, including Children of the Passage, Trinidad, The Stack-Up, Garth Fagan, Edna Guy recreations, D-Man in the Waters, and Strange Fruit.
    Arranged chronologically.
- Sound Recordings and Moving Images, 1994-2001 and undated, 78.75 linear feet (Box 20)
  Original elements for Free to Dance exist on film, Beta SP, VHS, DVD, DAT, DA-88, audiocassettes, and open reel audio tape. To cross reference elements, see the entries below. Titles and item numbers are taken from hand-written labels on the Beta SP tapes made at film transfer. DVDs or VHS copies of the Betas have the same item number.
  Audiocassette copies of the sound reels are numbered, but their numbers are not the same as the sound reels. UB numbers were assigned by DuArt Film & Video during editing.
  Additional tapes (without item numbers) are also in the collection. See the box list below.
  - Closer to the Truth #1: Donald McKayle, Nov. 30, 1998
    Item Number: 6001
    Camera Rolls: 10-14
  - Closer to the Truth #2: Donald McKayle, Talley Beatty, Nov. 30, 1998
    Item Number: 6002
    Camera Rolls: 15-19
  - Closer to the Truth #3: Talley Beatty, Nov. 30, 1998
    Item Number: 6003
    Camera Rolls: 20-21
  - Closer to the Truth #4: Talley Beatty, Nov. 30, 1998
    Item Number: 6004
    Camera Rolls: 25-28
  - Closer to the Truth #1: Eugene Van Grona, Nov. 12, 1998
    Item Number: 7002
    Camera Rolls: 1-4
    Sound Rolls: 1-2
  - Closer to the Truth #2: Eugene Van Grona, Henry Solomonoff, Nov. 12, 1998
    Item Number: 7003
    Camera Rolls: 5-9
    Sound Rolls: 3-5
    Audiocassettes: 1, 2
  - Trinidad: Molly Ayhe, Boscoe Holder, Mar. 26, 1998
    Item Number: 7004
    Camera Rolls: 26-30
    Sound Rolls: 21
    Audiocassettes: 3
  - Boscoe Holder, Trinidad B-Roll: House, Beach, Trees, Mar. 26, 1998
    Item Number: 7005
    Camera Rolls: 31-35
  - Trinidad: Stick Fighting, Field Work, Houses, Sea, Mar. 26, 1998
    Item Number: 7006
    Camera Rolls: 36-40
    Sound Rolls: 21, 22
    Audiocassettes: 3, 4
  - Trinidad: Beach, Estabs, Dance on Beach, City, Market, Mar. 26, 1998
    Item Number: 7007
    Camera Rolls: 41-45
    Sound Rolls: 22
    Audiocassettes: 4
  - Trinidad: Ray Watts, Katherine Dunham, Bellmont Stairs, Mar. 26, 1998
    Item Number: 7008
    Camera Rolls: 46-50
    Sound Rolls: 23, 24
    Audiocassettes: 5, 6
  - Katherine Dunham, undated
    Item Number: 7009
    Camera Rolls: 51-55
    Sound Rolls: 24, 25, 26
    Audiocassettes: 6, 7, 8
  - Katherine Dunham, undated
    Item Number: 7010
    Camera Rolls: 56-59
    Sound Rolls: 26, 27
    Audiocassettes: 8
  - Joe Nash, June 12, 1998
    Item Number: 7011
    Camera Rolls: 60-63
    Sound Rolls: 28
    Audiocassettes: 9
  - Joe Nash, June 12, 1998
    Item Number: 7012
    Camera Rolls: 64-67
  - Durham: Dayton Contemporary Dance Company, "Rainbow 'Round My Shoulder", June 22, 1998
    Item Number: 7013
    Camera Rolls: A68-71
    Sound Rolls: 29, x1
    UB Number: 10
  - Durham: Dayton Contemporary Dance Company, "Rainbow 'Round My Shoulder", June 22, 1998
    Item Number: 7014
    Camera Rolls: A72-75
    Sound Rolls: 29, 30, x1, x2
    UB Number: 11
  - Durham: Dayton Contemporary Dance Company, "The Stack-Up", June 22, 1998
    Item Number: 7015
    Camera Rolls: A76-79
    Sound Rolls: 31, x3
    UB Number: 12
  - Durham: Dayton Contemporary Dance Company, "The Stack-Up", "Rainbow 'Round My Shoulder", June 22, 1998
    Item Number: 7016
    Camera Rolls: A80-81, B68-69
    Sound Rolls: 31, x3, 29, x1
    UB Number: 13
  - Durham: Dayton Contemporary Dance Company, "Rainbow 'Round My Shoulder", June 22, 1998
    Item Number: 7017
    Camera Rolls: B70-73
    UB Number: 14
  - Durham: Dayton Contemporary Dance Company, "Rainbow 'Round My Shoulder", "The Stack-Up", June 22, 1998
    Item Number: 7018
    Camera Rolls: B74-77
    Sound Rolls: 29-31, x1, x2, x3
    UB Number: 15
  - Durham: Dayton Contemporary Dance Company, "The Stack-Up", June 22, 1998
    Item Number: 7019
    Camera Rolls: B78-81
    UB Number: 16
  - Durham: "Ostrich", "Mourner's Bench", "Las Desenamoradas", "Choros", June 23, 1998
    Item Number: 7020
    Camera Rolls: A82-86
    Sound Rolls: 3, 33, x4, x5
    UB Number: 17
  - Durham: Cleo Parker Robinson Dance Ensemble, "Levee Blues", "Barrelhouse Blues", June 23, 1998
    Item Number: 7021
    Camera Rolls: A87-91
    Sound Rolls: 33, 34, x5
    UB Number: 18
  - Durham: "Ostrich", "Mourner's Bench", "Las Desenamoradas", "Choros", June 24, 1998
    Item Number: 7022
    Camera Rolls: A92-93, B82-84
    Sound Rolls: 34, 32, x4
    UB Number: 19
  - Durham: "Las Desenamoradas", "Choros", "Barrelhouse Blues", June 24, 1998
    Item Number: 7023
    Camera Rolls: B85-89
    Sound Rolls: 32, 33, x4, x5
    UB Number: 20
  - Durham: Cleo Parker Robinson Dance Ensemble, "Levee Blues", June 24, 1998
    Item Number: 7024
    Camera Rolls: B90-91
    UB Number: 21
  - Richard Long, July 14, 1998
    Item Number: 7025
    Camera Rolls: A94-97
    Sound Rolls: 34
    Audiocassettes: 10
    UB Number: 22
  - Richard Long, Sylvius Moore, July 14, 1998
    Item Number: 7026
    Camera Rolls: A98-101
    Sound Rolls: 35, 36, 37
    Audiocassettes: 11
    UB Number: 23
  - Sylvius Moore, July 14, 1998
    Item Number: 7027
    Camera Rolls: A102-104
    Sound Rolls: 37, 38
    Audiocassettes: 12
    UB Number: 24
  - Carmencita Romero, July 20, 1998
    Item Number: 7028
    Camera Rolls: A105-108
    Sound Rolls: 30, 39
    Audiocassettes: 13
    UB Number: 25
  - Carmencita Romero, Charles Queenan, July 20, 1998
    Item Number: 7029
    Camera Rolls: A109-112
    Sound Rolls: 30, 39, 40
    Audiocassettes: 14, 15
    UB Number: 26
  - Charles Queenan, July 20, 1998
    Item Number: 7030
    Camera Rolls: A113-A116
    Sound Rolls: 40
    Audiocassettes: 16
    UB Number: 27
  - Charles Queenan, July 20, 1998
    Item Number: 7030A
    Camera Rolls: A117-120
    Audiocassettes: 17
    UB Number: 28
  - Walter Nicks and Philadanco, July 29, 1998
    Item Number: 7031
    Camera Rolls: 121-124
    Sound Rolls: 41, 41A
    UB Number: 29
  - Philadanco Sound Only, Dub of SR #41A, undated
    Item Number: 7031A
    Sound Rolls: 41A
    UB Number:
  - Walter Nicks and Philadanco, July 29, 1998
    Item Number: 7032
    Camera Rolls: 125-128
    Sound Rolls: 41, 41A, 42, 42A
    UB Number: 30
  - Philadanco Sound Only, Dub of SR #42A, undated
    Item Number: 7032A
    Sound Rolls: 42A
  - Walter Nicks and Philadanco, July 29, 1998
    Item Number: 7033
    Camera Rolls: 129-132
    Sound Rolls: 42, 42A
    UB Number: 31
  - Brenda Dixon Gottschild, July 29, 1998
    Item Number: 7034
    Camera Rolls: 133-136
    Sound Rolls: 42
    Audiocassettes: 18
    UB Number: 32
  - Brenda Dixon Gottschild, Walter Nicks and Philadanco, July 29, 1998
    Item Number: 7035
    Camera Rolls: 137-140
    Sound Rolls: 42, 43, 43A
    UB Number: 33
  - Walter Nicks and Philadanco, July 29, 1998
    Item Number: 7036
    Camera Rolls: 141-144
    Sound Rolls: 43, 43A
    UB Number: 34
  - Philadanco Sound Only, Dub of #43A, undated
    Item Number: 7036A
    Sound Rolls: 43A
  - Olatunjii, Merle Derby, Aug. 11, 1998
    Item Number: 7037
    Camera Rolls: 145-148
    Sound Rolls: 44, 44A
    UB Number: 35
  - Philadanco Sound Only, Dub of SR #44, undated
    Item Number: 7037A1
    Sound Rolls: 44
  - Philadanco Sound Only, Dub of SR #44, undated
    Item Number: 7037A2
  - Olatunjii, Merle Derby, Aug. 11, 1998
    Item Number: 7038
    Camera Rolls: 149
    UB Number: 36
  - Dayton Contemporary Dance Company, Sept. 14, 1998
    Item Number: 7039
    Camera Rolls: 150-153
    UB Number: 37
  - Donald McKayle, Ronald K. Brown, Sept. 14, 1998
    Item Number: 7040
    Camera Rolls: 154-156A
    UB Number: 38
  - Dayton Contemporary Dance Company, Sept. 14, 1998
    Item Number: 7041
    Camera Rolls: 157-161
    UB Number: 39
  - Dayton Contemporary Dance COMpany, Donald McKayle, Ronald K. Brown Interview, Sept. 14, 1998
    Item Number: 7042
    Camera Rolls: 162-167
    UB Number: 40
  - Vanoye Aikens, Sept. 23, 1998
    Item Number: 7043
    Camera Rolls: 168-171
    Sound Rolls: 47
    Audiocassettes: 19
    UB Number: 41
  - Vanoye Aikens, Joe Nash, Sept. 23, 1998
    Item Number: 7044
    Camera Rolls: 172-175
    Audiocassettes: 19, 20
    UB Number: 42
  - Joe Nash, Sept. 24, 1998
    Item Number: 7045
    Camera Rolls: 176-179
    Sound Rolls: 47, 48
    Audiocassettes: 20
    UB Number: 43
  - Joe Nash, Sept. 24, 1998
    Item Number: 7046
    Camera Rolls: 180-182
    Sound Rolls: 48
    Audiocassettes: 20A
    UB Number: 44
  - K. Hazzard Donald, Sept. 24, 1998
    Item Number: 7047
    Camera Rolls: 183-186
    Sound Rolls: 49, 50
    Audiocassettes: 21, 21A, 22
    UB Number: 45
  - K. Hazzard Donald, Sept. 24, 1998
    Item Number: 7048
    Camera Rolls: 187-190
    Sound Rolls: 50
    Audiocassettes: 21, 22
    UB Number: 46
  - K. Hazzard Donald, Eleo Pomare, Sept. 24, 1998
    Item Number: 7049
    Camera Rolls: 191-194
    Sound Rolls: 50, 51
    Audiocassettes: 21, 23
    UB Number: 47
  - Eleo Pomare, Sept. 28, 1998
    Item Number: 7050
    Camera Rolls: 195-198
    Sound Rolls: 51
    Audiocassettes: 23
    UB Number: 48
  - Eleo Pomare, Sept. 28, 1998
    Item Number: 7051
    Camera Rolls: 199-200
    Audiocassettes: 24
    UB Number: 49
  - Merle Derby, Oct. 1, 1998
    Item Number: 7052
    Camera Rolls: 201-204
    Sound Rolls: 49B
    Audiocassettes: 25
    UB Number: 50
  - Merle Derby, Dale Wasserman, Oct. 2, 1998
    Item Number: 7053
    Camera Rolls: 205-208, 211-212
    Audiocassettes: 25, 26, 27, 29
    UB Number: 51
  - Dale Wasserman, Oct. 2, 1998
    Item Number: 7054
    Camera Rolls: 207-210
    Audiocassettes: 27, 28
    UB Number: 52
  - Hampton: May Pleasant, Elaine Cooke, Nov. 10, 1998
    Item Number: 7055
    Camera Rolls: 213-216
    Sound Rolls: 50B, 51B
    Audiocassettes: 30
    UB Number: 53
  - Elaine Cook, Nov. 10, 1998
    Item Number: 7056
    Camera Rolls: 217-220
    Sound Rolls: 51B
    Audiocassettes: 31
    UB Number: 54
  - Church Tower, Delta Girls Choral, Alphas, Nov. 10, 1998
    Item Number: 7057
    Camera Rolls: 221-225
    Sound Rolls: 52
    Audiocassettes:
    UB Number: 55
  - AKA Girls Step, Nina Butts, Hampton, Nov. 10, 1998
    Item Number: 7058
    Camera Rolls: 225-228
    Audiocassettes: 32
    UB Number: 56
  - Carmen DeLavellade, Nov. 30, 1998
    Item Number: 7059
    Camera Rolls: 229-232
    Sound Rolls: 53
    Audiocassettes: 33A
    UB Number: 57
  - Carmen DeLavellade, Nov. 30, 1998
    Item Number: 7060
    Camera Rolls: 233-236
    Audiocassettes: 33, 33A
    UB Number: 58
  - Evelyn Pilcher, Nov. 30, 1998
    Item Number: 7061
    Camera Rolls: 237-240
    Sound Rolls: 53, 54
    Audiocassettes: 33, 34
    UB Number: 59
  - Muriel Mannings, Dec. 1, 1998
    Item Number: 7062
    Camera Rolls: 241-244
    Sound Rolls: 54
    Audiocassettes: 35
    UB Number: 60
  - Muriel Mannings, Miki Bord, Dec. 2, 1998
    Item Number: 7063
    Camera Rolls: 245-248
    Sound Rolls: 54, 55
    Audiocassettes: 35, 36
    UB Number: 61
  - Miki Bord, Dorene Richardson, Dec. 2, 1998
    Item Number: 7064
    Camera Rolls: 249-252
    Sound Rolls: 55
    Audiocassettes: 36
    UB Number: 62
  - Dorene Richardson, Dec. 2, 1998
    Item Number: 7065
    Camera Rolls: 253-256
    Audiocassettes: 37
    UB Number: 63
  - Jackie Goldman, Dec. 8, 1998
    Item Number: 7066
    Camera Rolls: 257-260
    Sound Rolls: 57
    Audiocassettes: 38
    UB Number: 64
  - Jackie Goldman, Dec. 8, 1998
    Item Number: 7067
    Camera Rolls: 261-264
    UB Number: 65
  - Jackie Goldman, Christine Lawson, Dec. 8, 1998
    Item Number: 7068
    Camera Rolls: 265-268
    Sound Rolls: 57, 58
    Audiocassettes: 38, 39
    UB Number: 66
  - Christine Lawson, Clive Thompson, Dec. 8, 1998
    Item Number: 7069
    Camera Rolls: 269-271
    Sound Rolls: 58, 59
    Audiocassettes: 39, 40
    UB Number: 67
  - Clive Thompson, Dec. 9, 1998
    Item Number: 7070
    Camera Rolls: 272-275
    Sound Rolls: 59, 60
    Audiocassettes: 40
    UB Number: 68
  - Clive Thompson, Dec. 9, 1998
    Item Number: 7071
    Camera Rolls: 276-279
    Sound Rolls: 60
    UB Number: 69
  - Bill T. Jones, Dec. 16, 1998
    Item Number: 7072
    Camera Rolls: 280-283
    UB Number: 70
  - Bill T. Jones, Dec. 16, 1998
    Item Number: 7073
    Camera Rolls: 284-287
    UB Number: 71
  - Bill T. Jones, Dec. 16, 1998
    Item Number: 7074
    Camera Rolls: 288-294
    UB Number: 72
  - Bill T. Jones, Zita Allen, Dec. 16, 1998
    Item Number: 7075
    Camera Rolls: 292-295
    Audiocassettes: 41
    UB Number: 73
  - Zita Allen, Dec. 16, 1998
    Item Number: 7076
    Camera Rolls: 296-299
    Audiocassettes: 42
    UB Number: 74
  - Zita Allen, Dec. 16, 1998
    Item Number: 7077
    Camera Rolls: 300
    Audiocassettes: 43
    UB Number: 75
  - Ruth Beckford, Dec. 21, 1998
    Item Number: 7078
    Camera Rolls: 301-304
    Sound Rolls: 64, 65, 66
    Audiocassettes: 44
    UB Number: 76
  - Ruth Beckford, Peter Wood, Dec. 21, 1998
    Item Number: 7079
    Camera Rolls: 305-308
    Sound Rolls: 66
    Audiocassettes: 44, 45
    UB Number: 77
  - Peter Wood, Dec. 21, 1998
    Item Number: 7080
    Camera Rolls: 309-310
    Audiocassettes: 45
    UB Number: 78
  - Jean Leon Destine, Dec. 22, 1998
    Item Number: 7081
    Camera Rolls: 311-314
    Sound Rolls: 67
    Audiocassettes: 46
    UB Number: 79
  - Jean Leon Destine, Chief Bey, Dec. 22, 1998
    Item Number: 7082
    Camera Rolls: 315-319
    Audiocassettes: 46, 47
    UB Number: 80
  - Chief Bey, Dec. 22, 1998
    Item Number: 7083
    Camera Rolls: 320-323
    Sound Rolls: 67, 68
    Audiocassettes: 47
    UB Number: 81
  - Christine Grey, Walter Nicks, Dec. 22, 1998
    Item Number: 7084
    Camera Rolls: 324-327
    Sound Rolls: 69
    Audiocassettes: 48
    UB Number: 82
  - Walter Nicks, Dec. 28, 1998
    Item Number: 7085
    Camera Rolls: 328-331
    Audiocassettes: 49
    UB Number: 83
  - Walter Nicks, Dec. 28, 1998
    Item Number: 7086
    Camera Rolls: 332-335
    Sound Rolls: 69, 70
    UB Number: 84
  - Dean Sheldon, Leon Bibb, Dec. 28, 1998
    Item Number: 7087
    Camera Rolls: 336-339
    Sound Rolls: 71
    Audiocassettes: 50, 51
    UB Number: 85
  - Leon Bibb, Dec. 28, 1998
    Item Number: 7088
    Camera Rolls: 340-343
    Audiocassettes: 51
    UB Number: 86
  - Leon Bibb, Dec. 28, 1998
    Item Number: 7089
    Camera Rolls: 344
    UB Number: 87
  - S'thembile West, Jan. 11, 1999
    Item Number: 7090
    Camera Rolls: 345-348
    Audiocassettes: 52
    UB Number: 88
  - S'thembile West, James Haskins, Jan. 11, 1999
    Item Number: 7091
    Camera Rolls: 349-352
    Audiocassettes: 53
    UB Number: 89
  - James Haskins, Jan. 11, 1999
    Item Number: 7092
    Camera Rolls: 353
    Audiocassettes: 54
    UB Number: 90
  - Richard Powell, Jan. 21, 1999
    Item Number: 7093
    Camera Rolls: 354-357
    Sound Rolls: 73
    Audiocassettes: 55
    UB Number: 91
  - Richard Powell, Jan. 21, 1999
    Item Number: 7094
    Camera Rolls: 358-361
    UB Number: 92
  - Chuck Davis, Jan. 21, 1999
    Item Number: 7095
    Camera Rolls: 362-365
    Sound Rolls: 74
    Audiocassettes: 56
    UB Number: 93
  - Chuck Davis, Jan. 21, 1999
    Item Number: 7096
    Camera Rolls: 366
    UB Number: 94
  - Rex Nettleford, Jan. 21, 1999
    Item Number: 7097
    Camera Rolls: 367-370
    Sound Rolls: 75
    Audiocassettes: 57
    UB Number: 95
  - Rex Nettleford, Jan. 22, 1999
    Item Number: 7098
    Camera Rolls: 371-374
    UB Number: 96
  - Rex Nettleford, Lynne Conner, Jan. 22, 1999
    Item Number: 7099
    Camera Rolls: 375-378
    Sound Rolls: 75, 76, 77
    Audiocassettes: 57, 58
    UB Number: 97
  - Lynne Conner, Marcia Heard, Jan. 22, 1999
    Item Number: 7100
    Camera Rolls: 379-382
    Sound Rolls: 77
    Audiocassettes: 58, 59
    UB Number: 98
  - Marcia Heard, Jan. 22, 1999
    Item Number: 7101
    Camera Rolls: 383-386
    Sound Rolls: 77, 78
    UB Number: 99
  - Marcia Heard, Jan. 22, 1999
    Item Number: 7102
    Camera Rolls: 387-389
    Sound Rolls: 78
    Audiocassettes: 59
    UB Number: 100
  - Sheri Williams, Gary Harris, Feb. 10, 1999
    Item Number: 7103
    Camera Rolls: 390-393
    Sound Rolls: 79
    Audiocassettes: 60
    UB Number: 101
  - Gary Harris, Dayton Contemporary Dance Company, Feb. 10, 1999
    Item Number: 7104
    Camera Rolls: 394-398
    Sound Rolls: 79, 80
    UB Number: 102
  - Dayton Contemporary Dance Company, Feb. 10, 1999
    Item Number: 7105
    Camera Rolls: 399-400
    Sound Rolls: 80
    UB Number: 103
  - Donald McKayle, Mar. 11, 1999
    Item Number: 7106
    Camera Rolls: 401-404
    UB Number: 104
  - Donald McKayle, Ted Thomas, Mar. 11, 1999
    Item Number: 7107
    Camera Rolls: 405-408
    Sound Rolls: 81
    Audiocassettes: 61
    UB Number: 105
  - Ted Thomas, Christa Gabri, Mar. 11, 1999
    Item Number: 7108
    Camera Rolls: 409-411
    Sound Rolls: 82
    Audiocassettes: 62
    UB Number: 106
  - Edna Guy, Ruth St. Denis, Angel Orensanz Center for the Arts, Mar. 11, 1999
    Item Number: 7109
    Camera Rolls: 412-415
    UB Number: 107
  - Edna Guy, Ruth St. Denis, Angel Orensanz Center for the Arts, Mar. 11, 1999
    Item Number: 7110
    Camera Rolls: 416-417
    UB Number: 108
  - Edna Guy, Ruth St. Denis, Valerie's Brownstone, Grant's Tomb, Jumel Terrace, Mar. 19, 1999
    Item Number: 7111
    Camera Rolls: 418-422
    UB Number: 109
  - Edna Guy, Ruth St. Denis, Abyssinian Church, Mar. 19, 1999
    Item Number: 7112
    Camera Rolls: 423-425
    UB Number: 110
  - Edna Guy, Artists Painting, Mar. 24, 1999
    Item Number: 7113
    Camera Rolls: 426-427
    UB Number: 111
  - Bill T. Jones and mother, Abdel Salaam, Apr. 15, 1999
    Item Number: 7114
    Camera Rolls: 428-431
    UB Number: 112
  - Abdell Salaam, Apr. 15, 1999
    Item Number: 7115
    Camera Rolls: 432-435
    UB Number: 113
  - Abdell Salaam, Apr. 15, 1999
    Item Number: 7116
    Camera Rolls: 436-437
    UB Number: 114
  - Forces of Nature Dance Company, Apr. 20, 1999
    Item Number: 7117
    Camera Rolls: 438-441
    UB Number: 115
  - Forces of Nature Dance Company, undated
    Item Number: 7118
    Camera Rolls: 442-445
    UB Number: 116
  - Forces of Nature Dance Company, undated
    Item Number: 7119
    Camera Rolls: 446-449
    UB Number: 117
  - Halifu Osmaje, Apr. 29, 1999
    Item Number: 7120
    Camera Rolls: 450-453
    Sound Rolls: 89
    Audiocassettes: 64, 64A
    UB Number: 118
  - Halifu Osmaje, Gus Solomans, Jr., Apr. 29, 1999
    Item Number: 7121
    Camera Rolls: 454-457
    Sound Rolls: 89, 90
    UB Number: 119
  - Gus Solomans, Jr., Apr. 29, 1999
    Item Number: 7122
    Camera Rolls: 458-460
    Sound Rolls: 90
    UB Number: 120
  - "D-Man in the Waters", June 21, 1999
    Item Number: 7123
    Camera Rolls: A460-463
    UB Number: 121
    The Item numbers on the Betas and VHS copies of 7123-7133 disagree, i.e., VHS 7123 is not a copy of Beta 7123. It appears, however, that all the material on Betas 7123-7133 is represented on VHS, just with mixed up ID numbers.
  - "D-Man in the Waters", June 21, 1999
    Item Number: 7124
    Camera Rolls: A464-467
    Sound Rolls: 90, 91
    UB Number: 122
  - "D-Man in the Waters", Chuck Davis, Farga, Isicathulo, Lamban, June 21, 1999
    Item Number: 7125
    Camera Rolls: A468-471
    Sound Rolls: 91, 92
    UB Number: 123
  - Chuck Davis, Lambari, Balente, Strange Fruit, Etude, June 23, 1999
    Item Number: 7126
    Camera Rolls: A472-475
    Sound Rolls: 92, 93
    UB Number: 124
  - Bill T. Jones, Etude, June 22, 1998
    Item Number: 7127
    Camera Rolls: A476
    UB Number: 125
  - D-Man in the Waters, June 22, 1998
    Item Number: 7128
    Camera Rolls: B460-461
    Audiocassettes: 65, 65A
    UB Number: 126
  - D-Man in the Waters, June 22, 1998
    Item Number: 7129
    Camera Rolls: B462-463
    UB Number: 127
  - D-Man in the Waters, June 23, 1999
    Item Number: 7130
    Camera Rolls: B464-465
    UB Number: 128
  - D-Man in the Waters, June 23, 1999
    Item Number: 7131
    Camera Rolls: B466-467
    UB Number: 129
  - D-Man in the Waters, Chuck Davis, Farga, Isicathulo, Lamban, June 23, 1999
    Item Number: 7132
    Camera Rolls: B468-471
    UB Number: 130
  - Chuck Davis, Lambari, Balente, Strange Fruit, Etude, June 23, 1999
    Item Number: 7133
    Camera Rolls: B472-476
    UB Number: 131
  - Katherine Dunham: Residence, Haiti, June 24, 1999
    Item Number: 7134
    Camera Rolls: UN1
    UB Number: 132
  - Hope Clark, Aug. 2, 1999
    Item Number: 7135
    Camera Rolls: 477-480
    Sound Rolls: 95
    Audiocassettes: 66
    UB Number: 133
  - Julie Belafonte, Aug. 2, 1999
    Item Number: 7136
    Camera Rolls: 481-484
    Sound Rolls: 96
    Audiocassettes: 67
    UB Number: 134
  - Julie Belafonte, Charles Queenan, Aug. 2, 1999
    Item Number: 7137
    Camera Rolls: 485-487
    UB Number: 135
  - Eloise Anderson, Sept. 3, 1999
    Item Number: 7138
    Camera Rolls: 509-512
    Sound Rolls: 102
    Audiocassettes: 72
    UB Number: 136
  - Eloise Anderson, Katherine Dunham, Sept. 7, 1999
    Item Number: 7139
    Camera Rolls: 513-516
    UB Number: 137
  - Katherine Dunham, Sept. 7, 1999
    Item Number: 7140
    Camera Rolls: 517-520
    Sound Rolls: 103
    Audiocassettes: 73
    UB Number: 138
  - Katherine Dunham, Sept. 7, 1999
    Item Number: 7141
    Camera Rolls: 521
    UB Number: 139
  - Jowale Zollar, Sept. 8, 1999
    Item Number: 7142
    Camera Rolls: 488-491
    Sound Rolls: 97
    Audiocassettes: 68
    UB Number: 140
  - Ron Brown, Sept. 8, 1999
    Item Number: 7143
    Camera Rolls: 492-495
    Sound Rolls: 98
    Audiocassettes: 69
    UB Number: 141
  - Rennie Harris, Sept. 8, 1999
    Item Number: 7144
    Camera Rolls: 496-497
    Sound Rolls: 99
    Audiocassettes: 70
    UB Number: 142
  - Buster Brown, Trisha Brown, Sept. 16, 1999
    Item Number: 7145
    Camera Rolls: 498-501
    Sound Rolls: 100
    Audiocassettes: 71
    UB Number: 143
  - Trisha Brown, Judith Jamison, Sept. 16, 1999
    Item Number: 7146
    Camera Rolls: 502-505
    Sound Rolls: 100, 101
    Audiocassettes: 71, no number
    UB Number: 144
  - Judith Jamison, Sept. 16, 1999
    Item Number: 7147
    Camera Rolls: 506-508
    UB Number: 145
  - Rosalynde LeBlanc, Oct. 21, 1999
    Item Number: 7148
    Camera Rolls: 522-525
    Sound Rolls: 104
    Audiocassettes: 74
    UB Number: 146
  - Geoffrey Holder, Oct. 21, 1999
    Item Number: 7149
    Camera Rolls: 526-529
    Sound Rolls: 105
    Audiocassettes: 75
    UB Number: 147
  - Dianne Walker, Oct. 21, 1999
    Item Number: 7150
    Camera Rolls: 530-533
    Sound Rolls: 105, 106
    Audiocassettes: 75, 76
    UB Number: 148
  - Dianne Walker, Garth Fagan, Oct. 21, 1999
    Item Number: 7151
    Camera Rolls: 534-537
    Sound Rolls: 106, 107
    Audiocassettes: 76, 77
    UB Number: 149
  - Garth Fagan, Oct. 21, 1999
    Item Number: 7152
    Camera Rolls: 538-539
    Sound Rolls: 107
    Audiocassettes: 77
    UB Number: 150
  - Jowale Zollar, Bill T. Jones, Oct. 21, 1999
    Item Number: 7153
    Camera Rolls: 540-543
    Sound Rolls: 108, 109
    Audiocassettes: 78, 79
    UB Number: 151
  - Zita Allen, Paul Jefferson, Dec. 21, 1999
    Item Number: 7154
    Camera Rolls: 544-547
    Sound Rolls: 110
    Audiocassettes: 81
    UB Number: 152
  - Paul Jefferson, Julia Foulkes, Dec. 21, 1999
    Item Number: 7155
    Camera Rolls: 548-551